savingforcollege.com 2011-12-01

# Privacy Policy Jfh Innovative, Llc

**Last Updated: December 17, 2010**

**JFH Innovative LLC, a New York corporation ("JFHI"), owns and operates the Web site located at the URL www.savingforcollege.com, and portions of other Web pages and Web content through which you have accessed this Privacy Policy (collectively, "savingforcollege.com"). By visiting, using and/or submitting information to savingforcollege.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy and the terms and conditions of JFHI's Agreement of Terms of Use located at<http://www.savingforcollege.com/terms_of_use/> (the "Terms of Use"). **

JFHI takes your privacy seriously, and has published this Privacy Policy to explain how JFHI treats all information you may submit to savingforcollege.com, except that information which is submitted pursuant to a sweepstakes entry. Refer to the Official Rules and Privacy Policy for each individual sweepstakes for JFHI's specific policies regarding information sharing and disclosure pursuant to sweepstakes entry. 

**Collection of Personally Identifiable Information**

Many of the features of savingforcollege.com are available to you without your providing personally identifiable information. Personally identifiable information generally includes information that could be used to determine your identity, such as your name, address, phone number, e-mail address, and birth date. The following are certain situations in which JFHI may collect personally identifiable information from you:

  * **Registration for Newsletters and Sweepstakes.** JFHI collects personally identifiable information from you if you register online for one of JFHI's newsletters and when you enter JFHI's sweepstakes. When you register online with JFHI, JFHI asks for personally identifiable information like your name, e-mail address, birth date, gender, ZIP code, occupation, industry, personal interests and other demographic information. 
  * **Use of Forums.** If you choose to transmit, submit or post information through JFHI's chat rooms, bulletin boards or other forums (the "Forums"), JFHI will collect that information you provide. JFHI retains this information as necessary to resolve disputes, provide customer support and troubleshoot problems as permitted by law and pursuant to JFHI's Terms of Use.
  * **Forms.** JFHI may collect personally identifiable information from you if you choose to fill out any forms, profiles, or surveys on savingforcollege.com.
  * **Correspondence.** If you send JFHI personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send JFHI correspondence about your activities or postings on savingforcollege.com, JFHI may choose to collect such information into a file specific to you.
  * **Business Partners.** JFHI may receive your personally identifiable information from one of JFHI's business partners.

**Use of Personally Identifiable Information**

JFHI uses your personally identifiable information as follows:

  * to improve JFHI's marketing and promotional efforts, analyze site usage, improve JFHI's content and product offerings, and customize JFHI's content, layout, and services;
  * to contact you and deliver information to you that, in some cases, is targeted to your interests, such as targeted banner advertisements, administrative notices, product offerings, and communications relevant to your use of savingforcollege.com;
  * to fulfill your requests for certain products and services;
  * for market research, project planning, troubleshooting problems, detecting and protecting against error, fraud or other criminal activity, to enforce JFHI's Terms of Use, for other internal purposes, and as otherwise described to you at the time of collection; and
  * as otherwise set forth in this Privacy Policy.

You expressly agree to JFHI's use of your personally identifiable information as set forth in this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use.

**Disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information**

Unless you are entering one of JFHI's sweepstakes, JFHI does not currently sell your personally identifiable information. The following describes some of the ways that your personally identifiable information may be disclosed in the normal scope of business:

  * **Advertisers.** JFHI may aggregate personally identifiable information and disclose such information in a non-personally identifiable manner to advertisers and other third parties for their marketing and promotional purposes. For example, JFHI may aggregate personally identifiable information and disclose it to network advertisers in a non-personally identifiable manner as set forth in the section entitled "Network Advertisers," set forth below. _JFHI does not disclose your information in a personally identifiable manner to such third party advertisers without your consent._
  * **External Service Providers.** There are a number of separate services offered by third parties, including, without limitation, JFHI's affiliates, that JFHI refers to as external service providers that may be complementary to your use of savingforcollege.com (e.g. financial institutions, financial planners, legal and tax professionals). If you choose to use these separate services, disclose information to the external service providers, and/or grant them permission to collect information about you, then their use of your information is governed by their privacy policy. With your consent, JFHI may provide some of your personal information to the external service provider offering such services, for your convenience. To prevent JFHI's disclosure of your personally identifiable information to an external service provider, you can decline such consent or simply not use their services. You should evaluate the practices of external services providers before deciding to use their services.
  * **Internal Service Providers.** JFHI may use third parties that JFHI refers to as internal service providers to facilitate or outsource one or more aspects of JFHI's business, product and service operations that JFHI provides to you (e.g., technology, Forums, newsletters/alerts, analytical tools, advertising campaign management) and therefore JFHI may provide some of your personal information directly to these internal service providers. These internal service providers are subject to confidentiality agreements with JFHI or other legal restrictions that prohibit their use of the information JFHI provides them for any other purpose except to facilitate the specific outsourced JFHI related operation, unless you have explicitly agreed or given your prior permission to them for additional uses. In some instances, the internal service provider may collect information directly from you. In these cases, you will be notified of the involvement of the internal service provider, and all additional information you provide them and their additional uses will be strictly up to you. If you provide additional information to an internal service provider directly, then their use of your personally identifiable information is governed by their applicable privacy policy.

Notwithstanding the foregoing, JFHI reserves the right (and you authorize JFHI) to share or disclose your personally identifiable information when JFHI determines, in its sole discretion, that the disclosure of your personally identifiable information is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against you if:

  * you are or may be violating this Privacy Policy or JFHI's Terms of Use;
  * you are interfering with another's rights or property, including, without limitation, JFHI's rights or property; 
  * you are violating any applicable law, rule or regulation; 
  * necessary or required by any applicable law, rule or regulation; and/or 
  * requested by authorities in the event of any act of terrorism or instance of local, regional or national emergency.

Personally identifiable information and other personal information collected from you may also be transferred to a third party as a result of a sale, acquisition, merger, reorganization, other transfer or bankruptcy (a "Transfer") involving JFHI and/or its affiliates. JFHI specifically reserves the right to transfer personally identifiable information collected from savingforcollege.com, and any of its databases, together with any personally identifiable information contained therein, to a third party in connection with a Transfer, and nothing in this Privacy Policy is intended to interfere with the ability of JFHI to transfer all or part of its business and/or assets (including savingforcollege.com) to an affiliate or independent third party at any time, for any purpose, without any limitation whatsoever.

In addition, due to the existing regulatory environment, JFHI cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. By way of example (without limiting the foregoing), JFHI may be forced to disclose personal information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances or third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. Therefore, although JFHI uses industry standard practices to protect your privacy, JFHI does not promise, and you should not expect, that your personally identifiable information or private communications will always remain private.

**NOTE: If you are submitting personally identifiable information pursuant to sweepstakes entry, JFHI reserves the right to share, loan, rent and/or sell the personally identifiable information that you submit with its affiliates and other third parties. Please refer to the Official Rules and Privacy Policy for each individual sweepstakes for the specific guidelines regarding information sharing and disclosure.**

**Network Advertising**

JFHI may use third-party advertising companies for marketing, advertising and promotional purposes, as well as to serve advertisements to you. Using third-party advertising companies helps us and third-party advertisers better determine which advertisements or content to serve to you. For example, the third-party advertisers may use information regarding your visits to savingforcollege.com and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services, that third party advertisers believe will be of interest to you.

The types of information that may be collected by third-party advertising companies include the following:

  * the type of Internet browser you use; 
  * the type of computer operating system you use; 
  * the domain name of a Web site you visit, as well as information related to Web sites and Web pages you are viewing when an advertisement is requested; 
  * whether or not you visit specific pages of savingforcollege.com or other Web sites;
  * the location of your Internet service provider's point of presence; 
  * the date and time of a visit to a Web site;
  * search keywords passed from another server; 
  * the number of times you have clicked on an advertisement; and
  * other interactions between you and a Web site.

**If you would like to opt-out of third-party advertising companies' use of such information,[click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).** If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/consumer/).

**Opt- Out and Changes to Personally Identifiable Information and Use Preferences**

You may at any time request a copy of JFHI's record of your personally identifiable information, change your personally identifiable information or use preferences, or opt-out of JFHI's use of your personally identifiable information by contacting JFHI via any of the methods set forth below:

  * Via telephone: (585) 286-5426
  * Via fax: (585) 286-5428 
  * Via mail: JFH Innovative LLC, 1151 Pittsford Victor Rd, Ste 103, Pittsford, NY 14534
  * Via email: [support@savingforcollege.com](mailto:support@savingforcollege.com)
  * Via online link: <http://www.savingforcollege.com/>

If you would like to opt-out of third-party advertising companies' use of your information for the network advertising purposes described above, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

**Newsletters and CAN-SPAM Compliance**

Savingforcollege.com sends only verified, double-opt-in e-mail newsletters, specifically requested by JFHI subscribers. Subscriptions to Savingforcollege.com newsletters are verified by sending an e-mail confirmation to your e-mail address, which requires a positive response before an e-mail address is added to JFHI's list. Savingforcollege.com is fully compliant with the Controlling the Assault of Non-Solicited Pornography and Marketing Act of 2003.

**Cookie technology**

"Cookies" are alphanumeric identifiers in the form of text files that are inserted and stored by your Web browser on your computer's hard drive. JFHI, its external service providers, internal service providers, and third-party advertising companies, may set and access cookies on your computer to track and store preferential information about you. JFHI, and its external service providers, internal service providers, and third-party advertising companies gather anonymous information about you through cookie technology on an aggregate level only. For example, a third-party advertising company may assign a cookie (and a Web beacon, described below) to you, to limit the amount of times you see a particular advertisement or to help better determine which advertisements to serve to you. Please note that most Internet browsers will allow you to stop cookies from being stored on your computer and to delete cookies stored on your computer.

**Web beacons**

"Web beacons", also called single-pixels (1x1) or clear GIFs, are electronic images that allow a Web site to access cookies and help track marketing campaigns and general usage patterns of visitors to those Web sites. Web beacons can recognize certain types of information, such as cookie numbers, time and date of a page view, and a description of the page where the Web beacon is placed. No personally identifiable information about you is shared with third parties through the use of Web beacons.

  * **Internal use of Web beacons.** JFHI may use Web beacons internally to count users and recognize users through cookies. Access to cookies helps JFHI personalize your experience when you visit savingforcollege.com.
  * **Email.** JFHI may include Web beacons in HTML-formatted email messages that JFHI or its affiliates or agents send. Including Web beacons in email messages helps JFHI determine your interest in and the effectiveness of such emails.
  * **External use of Web beacons.** JFHI may also use Web beacons externally. For example, JFHI may report aggregate information about Savingforcollege.com users, such as demographic and usage information, to its partners and other third parties. JFHI may also include other company's Web beacons within Savingforcollege.com.

**Security**

Personally identifiable information you submit to JFHI is password-protected for your privacy and security. In certain areas JFHI uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions. In the unlikely event that an unauthorized third party compromises JFHI security measures, JFHI will not be responsible for any damages directly or indirectly caused by an unauthorized third party's ability to view, use or disseminate such information.

**Links to Other Web sites**

Savingforcollege.com may include links to other third party Web sites. Such links are not an endorsement by JFHI of those Web sites and/or the products or services offered there. Third party Web sites may have different privacy policies and JFHI is not responsible for the privacy practices of those third party Web sites. If you click on a link to a third party Web site, JFHI encourages you to check the privacy policy of that Web site, as it may differ substantially from that of this Privacy Policy.

**Access and Use of savingforcollege.com**

Savingforcollege.com is intended to be accessed and used only by adults and is not directed to children under the age of 18. JFHI does not knowingly permit registration or submission of personally identifiable information by anyone under the age of 18.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

JFHI reserves the right to update, amend and/or change this Privacy Policy at any time in its sole discretion and without notice. Updates to this Privacy Policy will be posted here. Any information JFHI collects from you online is subject only to JFHI's most current Privacy Policy. You are encouraged to revisit this Privacy Policy from time to time in order to review any changes that have been made. JFHI's last update was December 17, 2010. Your continued access and use of savingforcollege.com following the posting of any such changes shall automatically be deemed your acceptance of the same.

**Questions or Concerns**

If you have questions, comments, concerns or feedback regarding this Privacy Policy, send an e-mail to [webmaster@Savingforcollege.com](mailto:webmaster@Savingforcollege.com).

**Governing Law; Arbitration**

This Privacy Policy is to be governed by and construed in accordance with the internal laws of the State of Florida, without regard for principles of conflicts of laws. Any civil action, claim, dispute or proceeding arising out of, or relating to, this Privacy Policy shall be referred to final and binding arbitration, before a single arbitrator, under the commercial arbitration rules of the American Arbitration Association in Palm Beach County, Florida. You and JFHI shall select the arbitrator, and if you and JFHI are unable to reach agreement on selection of the arbitrator within thirty (30) days after the notice of arbitration is served, then the American Arbitration Association shall select the arbitrator. Arbitration shall not commence until the party requesting it has deposited One Thousand Dollars ($1,000.00) with the arbitrator as a retainer for the arbitrator's fees and costs. The party requesting arbitration shall advance such sums as are required from time to time by the arbitrator to pay the arbitrator's fees and costs until the prevailing party is determined or the parties have agreed in writing to an alternate allocation of fees and costs.

Judgment upon any award rendered by the arbitrator shall be final, binding and conclusive upon you and JFHI, and your and JFHI's respective administrators, executors, legal representatives, successors and assigns, and may be entered in any court of competent jurisdiction. Notwithstanding the previous sentence, in no event shall either you or JFHI be entitled to punitive, special, indirect or consequential damages, and both you and JFHI hereby waive your rights to any punitive, special, indirect or consequential damages, including, but not limited to, damages for any loss of profit, revenue or business.

**Miscellaneous**

If any portion of this Privacy Policy is deemed unlawful, void or unenforceable by any arbitrator, this Privacy Policy as a whole shall not be deemed unlawful, void or unenforceable, but only that portion of this Privacy Policy that is unlawful, void or unenforceable shall be stricken from this Privacy Policy.

The headings contained in this Privacy Policy are for convenience of reference only, are not to be considered a part of this Privacy Policy, and shall not limit or otherwise affect in any way the meaning or interpretation of this Privacy Policy.

All covenants, agreements, representations and warranties made in this Privacy Policy, as may be amended by JFHI from time to time, shall survive your acceptance of this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use represent the entire understanding and agreement between you and JFHI regarding the subject matter of the same, and supersede all other previous agreements, understandings and/or representations regarding the same.
